CURRICULUM VITAE

LOUIS ASIEDU ACHEAMPONG

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Address: P.O. Box AT 1973,

Achimota-Market

Email: louisacheampong666@gmail.com

Telephone: +233-501541232

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Dedicated front-end developer with diverse operational experience in both IT development and Design. Experience in creating customized solutions to address specific customer requirements, improve overall productivity, and dramatically increase efficiency. Passionate about software development and architecture.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Proficient with Microsoft Office applications.
- Very conversant with the use of Adobe Photoshop.
- Very conversant with the use of the Internet.
- Good in Web Development (HTML, CSS, MySQL, JavaScript & PHP).
- Exceptional communication skills, including explaining complex technical information to non-technical personnel in an understandable way.
- Very conversant with the use of Sage Enterprise Management HR (formerly known as Sage X3 People).
- Very conversant with the use of SAP Crystal Reporting tool.
- Very conversant with the use of Microsoft Structured Query Language (SQL).
- Implementation and configurations of ERPs such as Sage X3, Sage X3 People, Sage Enterprise Intelligence, SAP B1 Cloud
- Writing and updating technical documents for team and other departments

- Performing repairs quickly, correctly and ethically.
- Built ecommerce web applications to sell products online, help increased companies' sales.

OTHER SKILLS

- Communicate effectively with clients and industry professionals to maintain complete and current working knowledge
- Excellent time and management skills.
- Provide effective solutions to meet stated objectives and goals.
- Strong interpersonal and communication skills.
- Extremely organized and results-oriented.
- Able to work according to time limits.
- Have the ability to identify fine details.
- Ability to perform multiple tasks and a teamwork player

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

|October 2020 — Present|

Multisoft Solutions Limited

- Provide analytical and design expertise; system configuration; data mapping; testing, and client support of live payroll processing (Payroll, ESS & HR).
- Provides ongoing support to clients on live projects.
- Designing and customization of reports.
- Communicate with Client Staff at the Highest Level.
- Prepare, Plan and Schedule Training Sessions.

- Go Live Take-on and Hand Holding Support.
- Custom build of new screens and fields in Sage X3 ERP and Sage X3 People.
- Train end-users on how to navigate through ERPs.
- Virtual Machines (VMs) building and restoration.
- Installation and configurations of a 5-tier installation for SAP B1 Cloud
- Help developed web applications; timesheet web portal, Customer Relationship Management (CRM), and Payroll application for Multisoft Solutions Limited.

Financial Crime and Compliance Analyst — National Service Personnel | September 2019—August 2020 |

Standard Chartered Bank Ltd.

- Conducting client due diligence.
- Conducting transaction monitoring and surveillance(TM/TS) investigations to fight money laundering.
- Reporting unusual transactions and suspicious activities in clients' accounts.
- Assisting in implementing effective Anti-bribery and corruption programs.
- Assisting in implementing effective procedures to reduce money-laundering risk.

Artisan — Intern

|Jun 2018-Aug2018|

Ze-Y-Ze Leather Works

- Produced Shoes locally to be on Par with international standards
- Designed new marketing strategies in the sale of the locally made shoes.
- Designing of patterns and templates during shoe production.

EDUCATION

BA Integrated Rural Arts and Industry

|September 2015 — Jun 2019|

Kwame Nkrumah University of Science & Technology

Presbyterian Boys' Senior High

|October 2012 — May

2015 | Kwame Nkrumah University of Science & Technology

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Enjoy reading, especially historical biographies and watching comic movies.
- Play video games and practice on my coding abilities.

REFERENCES

Available upon request.